He's just taking up space!
RocketMan is a comedy, family, science fiction film directed by Stuart Gillard.
An accident-prone and obnoxious geek joins a NASA space mission to Mars.
During the flight, he manages to put himself and the entire crew in jeopardy, but is in danger of emerging as a
hero when his new colleagues need him to save them from the unforgiving surface of the red planet.
Fred Z. Randall, played by Harland Williams.
Julie Ford, played by Jessica Lundy.
Wild Bill Overbeck, played by William Sadler.
Paul Wick, played by Jeffrey DeMunn.
Ben Stevens, played by James Pickens Jr..
Bud Nesbitt, played by Beau Bridges.
RocketMan (also written as Rocket Man) is a 1997 American comic science fiction film produced by Walt
Disney Pictures and Caravan Pictures, and distributed by Buena Vista Pictures Distribution.
Directed by Stuart Gillard, it stars Harland Williams,
Jessica Lundy, William Sadler, and Jeffrey DeMunn.
The film was released on October 10, 1997.
It received negative reviews from critics and grossed $15.4 million.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.